

MAJA BUKOWSKA

Junior Software Developer with Python

For almost 2 years I have gained a lot of valuable experience in software development. I am currently working as a Junior Software Developer, focusing on content automation. I am looking for a position in a similar area of expertise to provide the best value to my future employer.

CONTACT ME

- in www.linkedin.com/in/majabukowska
- https://github.com/majabukowska
- +48 668 562 411
- https://majabukowska.com

SKILLS

- Python (flask, pyspark) and Java
- C, C++ and basics of Assembly
- SQL and R
- Airflow / Docker
- Linux / Windows
- basics of Hadoop and Kubernetes
- HTML, JS, CSS
- GIT/GITHUB and GITLAB
- advanced in English
- fluent in Polish
- Jira / Confluence / TestRail

INTERESTS

- playing video games
- playing the piano

WORK EXPERIENCE

>> JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Wirtualna Polska

February 2023 - now

Responsible for the automatization of articles using **Python**, **Java** and **Flask**. Acquiring new skills, such as **Hadoop**, **Hive**, **SQLite**, **Kubernetes**, **Spark** and **GraphQL**

>> BIG DATA INTERN

Wirtualna Polska

November 2022 - February 2023 (3 months)

Working on **content automation** using **Python** and **Java** in a team of 4. Learning new skills such as **API calls, Docker and Airflow.**

>> QUALITY ASSURANCE TESTER

Q-LOC

October 2021 - September 2022 (1 year)

Manual game tester, working in teams of 10-20, completed numerous trainings about Excel, Jira and Confluence.

EDUCATION

>> UNIVERSITY OF GDAŃSK

September 2021 - now 3rd year student of **Computer Science**

>> III HIGHSCHOOL IN GDAŃSK

2018 - 2021 profile:

mathematics, physics and informatics

CERTIFICATES

>> ONLINE PYTHON PROGRAMMING COURSE

Codecademy Python Course

>> ONLINE SQL PROGRAMMING COURSE

Codecademy SQL Course

>> CERTIFICATE IN ADVANCED ENGLISH

British Council